(Leonard:)Preach.
(Sheldon:)And as
an added bonus,
the word "touché" comes
from fencing.
(Sheldon:)It would be our only opportunity
to use it
(Sheldon:)in a non-metaphorical sense.
(Leonard:)What about a game of tag
on a French schoolyard?
Ah, touché.
(Stuart:)Thanks for coming by.
(Bernadette:)Sure. So how can we help?
(Stuart:)Well, I know
more women are
(Stuart:)buying comics than ever,
but for some reason,
I-I can't get
'em in here.
(Penny:)All right, well,
what have you tried so far?
Uh, I've-I've been stocking
more female-oriented titles.
(Stuart:)Uh, in the bathroom, I folded
the end of the toilet paper
(Stuart:)into a triangle.
(Howard:)And,
uh,
(Stuart:)you are now sitting
in the official
(Stuart:)breastfeeding area.
(Penny:)Really? In a comic book store?
Oh,
don't worry. I-I've got
a camera right up here,
(Stuart:)so I could watch
from the counter
(Stuart:)and make sure guys
aren't being pervs.